<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="app_name">Fundamental Browser</string>
    <string name="space_redirected_space">" (redirected) "</string>
    <string name="failed_to_parse">Failed to parse ‘%1$s’</string>
    <string name="log">Log</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="true_lowercase">true</string>
    <string name="false_lowercase">false</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="main_url_field_hint">Enter URL or text</string>
    <string name="main_search_field_hint1">Text to find</string>
    <string name="main_search_field_hint2">Text to find</string>
    <string name="decode">Decode</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="paste">Paste</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="text_default">Default</string>
    <string name="tap_to_set">Tap to set</string>
    <string name="main_button_load">Load</string>
    <string name="main_button_run">Run</string>
    <string name="settings_title_options">Options</string>
    <string name="allow_javascript">Allow JavaScript</string>
    <string name="load_images">Load images</string>
    <string name="load_resources">Load resources</string>
    <string name="setting_foreground_logging">Foreground logging</string>
    <string name="accept_cookies">Accept cookies</string>
    <string name="accept_3rd_party_cookies">Accept third-party cookies</string>
    <string name="settings_title_max_log_msg">Max log messages</string>
    <string name="settings_max_log_msg_extra_text">This is the maximum number of log messages.</string>
    <string name="settings_title_search_url">Search URL</string>
    <string name="settings_search_url_extra_text">This is the URL that will be used when the search button is pressed, and will be joined with the search keywords to form an actual URL. The search button can only be used when this is set.\nExample: <code>https://example.com/search?q=</code></string>
    <string name="settings_title_experimental">Experimental</string>
    <string name="settings_title_clear_data">Clear data</string>
    <string name="clear_cache">Clear cache</string>
    <string name="clear_usernames_passwords">Clear usernames and passwords</string>
    <string name="clear_cookies">Clear cookies</string>
    <string name="settings_title_about">About</string>
    <string name="settings_text1">The source code of this app is available at https://github.com/sls1005/FundamentalBrowser, under the MIT License.</string>
    <string name="settings_text2">Disclaimer: JavaScript is a trademark or registered trademark of Oracle Corporation.</string>
    <string name="see_doc">See documentation</string>
    <string name="see_libs">See open source libraries used</string>
    <string name="remove_spaces_and_linebreaks_when_loading">Remove spaces and linebreaks when loading a URL</string>
    <string name="switch_remove_spaces_and_linebreaks_extra_text">It is recommended to turn this on.</string>
    <string name="show_button_run">Show button for running input as a script</string>
    <string name="switch_show_button_run_extra_text">This only works if JavaScript is enabled.</string>
    <string name="use_customized_user_agent">Use customized user agent</string>
    <string name="switch_custom_user_agent_extra_text">When disabled or not set, the default will be used.\n\n<b>Warning:</b> Please note that the use of highly customized user agent may result in privacy-related issues as described in https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc7231#section-9.7 .</string>
    <string name="desktop_mode">Desktop mode</string>
    <string name="switch_desktop_mode_extra_text">This is implemented by changing the user agent of this browser and thus can result in privacy-related issues as described in https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc7231#section-9.7 .\nIf this doesn\'t work, please consider using a custom user agent. See below for more information about customized user agents.</string>
    <string name="settings_title_advanced_sertings">Advanced settings</string>
    <string name="allow_http">HTTP-compatible mode</string>
    <string name="switch_allow_http_extra_text">Allow using HTTP (not HTTPS) as the communication protocol.\n\n<b>Warning:</b> HTTP is an insecure protocol and is different from HTTPS. It is recommended to keep this off unless you are testing your own server in LAN.</string>
    <string name="manually_set_languages">Set preferred languages</string>
    <string name="add_language">Add a language</string>
    <string name="switch_manually_set_languages_extra_string">This specifies the preferred languages of webpages, not the language of the UI.\nWhen disabled, the default will be used. If enabled but not set, no language tag will be sent.\nIf this doesn\'t work, please consider changing the language of this app. If your device supports doing so, the option for changing the language of this application will appear in the device settings.\nA website may ignore this.\n\n<b>Warning:</b> Please note that the use of highly customized language tags may result in privacy-related issues as described in https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc7231#section-9.7 .</string>
    <string name="clear_log_before_running_script">Clear log before running a script</string>
    <string name="autoscroll_log_msgs">Autoscroll log messages</string>
    <string name="allow_js_when_loading_url_that_is_from_another_app">Allow the use of JavaScript when loading a URL that is from another application</string>
    <string name="ask_before_loading_url_that_is_from_another_app">Ask before loading a URL that is from another application</string>
    <string name="confirm_following_redirection_to_load_page">Do you want to follow the redirection to load the page of ‘%1$s’?</string>
    <string name="ask_before_following_redirection">Ask before following redirection</string>
    <string name="switch_ask_before_following_redirection_extra_text">When enabled, this app will no longer automatically follow redirection.</string>
    <string name="show_advanced_developer_tools">Advanced developer tools</string>
    <string name="switch_show_advanced_developer_tools_extra_text_part1">Show advanced developer tools in the ‘More’ submenu of this application.</string>
    <string name="switch_show_advanced_developer_tools_extra_text_part2">Even if this is disabled, you can still use common developer tools such as the JavaScript console (if it is enabled) and the log, and can still view the source code of a web page or the certificate of a website. This option currently only covers less common tools.</string>
    <string name="auto_turn_urls_in_log_into_links">Automatically turn URLs in the log into links</string>
    <string name="switch_auto_link_urls_in_log_extra_text">Not all URLs will be turned into links. This app will selectively link the URLs. The more likely a URL would point to a page (or resource like image) on the web or to a file in the cache, the more likely it will be linked by this app. When you click a link in the log, it will be opened in this app; it will work offline if the file is still in the cache.</string>
    <string name="disable_dynamic_colors">Disable dynamic colors</string>
    <string name="switch_disable_dynamic_colors_extra_text">When this is turned on and the theme of this app is set to a theme other than the default, the colors of the UI of this app will not change according to system settings. There is, however, no guarantee that the colors would change according to system settings while this is turned off.</string>
    <string name="number_field_title1">Enter a number</string>
    <string name="url_field_title1">Enter a URL</string>
    <string name="string_field_title_1">Enter text</string>
    <string name="language_selection_title1">Select a language</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="language_selection_extra_text">The higher the weight, the higher the priority is. A language with higher priority is considered preferred. Default means highest priority.</string>
    <string name="repeat_to_close">Repeat the gesture to close this window</string>
    <string name="open_here">Open here</string>
    <string name="dont_load">Don\'t load</string>
    <string name="try_encryption">Try encryption</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_hide_tool_bar">Hide the tool bar</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_show_or_hide_url_bar">Show/hide URL bar</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_edit_url">Edit URL</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="menu1_js">JavaScript</string>
    <string name="menu1_foreground_logging">Foreground logging</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_search_content">Search content</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_search_in_log">Search in log</string>
    <string name="menu1_item_more">More</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_new_window">New window</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_open_in_another_app">Open in another app</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_view_log">View log</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_clear_log">Clear log</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_open_in_another_window">Open this page in another window</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_view_source">View the source code of this page</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_copy_url">Copy current URL as plain text</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_copy_url_as_link">Copy current URL as link</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_view_cert">View the certificate of this website</string>
    <string name="menu1_action_find_robots_txt">Find the ‘robots.txt’ of this website</string>
    <string name="error">Error: %1$s</string>
    <string name="error1">Error: Search URL is not set. Please set it in Settings.</string>
    <string name="error2">Please enter some keywords.</string>
    <string name="error3">Please enter a URL.</string>
    <string name="error4">Error: Empty URL</string>
    <string name="error5">Error: Couldn\'t find an application that can handle this uri.</string>
    <string name="error6">Error: Couldn\'t find an application other than this that can handle this uri.</string>
    <string name="error7">Error: Manually loading a URL of ‘%1$s’ scheme is not allowed.</string>
    <string name="error_no_cert">No certificate provided.</string>
    <string name="js_not_enabled">JavaScript must be enabled in order to run code.</string>
    <string name="warning"><b>Warning:</b></string>
    <string name="warnings"><b>Warnings:</b></string>
    <string name="cannot_display_pdf">" This app can\'t display PDF."</string>
    <string name="protocol_is_insecure">" The protocol is insecure."</string>
    <string name="warning_not_https">[Warning] ‘%1$s’ looks unsafe as its protocol seems to be HTTP rather than HTTPS.</string>
    <string name="method_was">" The method was ‘%1$s’."</string>
    <string name="blocked_but_can_change_in_settings">" Blocked. This behavior can be changed in settings."</string>
    <string name="view_privacy_policy">View the privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title1">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">1. This is a notice, not a legal document.\n\n2. When using this app, some of the information you provide, possibly including, but not limited to, a customized so-called ‘user agent’ or user-selected language tags, may be stored in the device by this app. Such data may be stored unencrypted.\n\n3. When the user visits a website by using this app, some information provided by the user, notably a customized user agent or user-selected language tags, may be sent to the website. Depending on the protocol, such data may be sent unencrypted.\n\n4. This application will not intentionally collect your information beyond what it should as a browser. In addition, it will never intentionally help you to hide your identity on the net nor prevent you from hiding your identity on the net.\n\n5. For more details about how this application collects and uses information, please see the source code of this application.</string>
    <string name="confirm_manually_setting_language_tags">Do you want to manually set the language tags?</string>
    <string name="confirm_opening_url_with_another_app1">Do you want to open this URL with another application?</string>
    <string name="confirm_opening_url_with_another_app_warning1"><b>Warning:</b> you are the one responsible for any damage caused by this action, so please read the URL/URI carefully, especially if it starts with ‘<b><code>intent:</code></b>’.</string>
    <string name="confirm_loading_page">Do you want to load the page of ‘%1$s’?</string>
    <string name="doc_title1">1. UI</string>
    <string name="doc_title1_1">i. The URL bar</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_1_1">The URL bar of this app is a little different from that of other browsers. It is still the place where the URL is displayed or edited, but now it is usually hidden and only shows up when the user needs it.\n\nWhen you need to see the URL bar, tap on the ‘<code>://</code>’ symbol if it is present in the top bar, or use the ‘Show/hide URL bar’ or ‘Edit URL’ option from the menu that is opened by tapping the three-dot icon in the top bar. Tapping the ‘<code>://</code>’ symbol once again (if it is present) will close the URL bar if it is already opened.\n\nThe URL bar allows multiline editing, that is, text that is too long will be wrapped to the next line. This makes it easier to view and edit when the URL is very long.\n\nThere are several buttons at the bottom of the URL bar. Those are:\n</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_1_2"><b>Load</b>: load the web page corresponding to a given URL. Unlike the ‘Search’ button, this does not do search.\n\n<b>Search</b>: search the web by using the text in the URL field as keywords. Only usable if the ‘search URL’ is set. Unlike the ‘Load’ button, this will not load a URL but… will search for it.\n\n<b>Copy</b>: copy the text in the URL field, or the selected text in the URL field, if any.\n\n<b>Paste</b>: paste the text to the URL field, either at the end of text or at the selected position if any text is selected.\n\n<b>Clear</b>: clear the URL field, removing all text.\n\n<b>Restore</b>: replace any text in the URL field with a previously loaded URL. This can also be used if the field is empty, in which case the previously loaded URL will still be restored, if any.\n\n<b>Decode</b>: decode the URL if it is pct-encoded. See https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc3986 for more details about pct-encoding.\n\n<b>Close</b>: close the URL bar.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title1_2">ii. The main window</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_2">This is where the web page is displayed.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title1_3">iii. The log</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_3">The log is a record of the web requests this app has made, including the requests for images, scripts, data (e.g., JSON) and other kinds of resources. It also contains the output of each script that has been run.\n\nTo open the log, use the ‘view log’ option from the option menu. The option is only available if there is anything in the log.\n\nEach request-related entry consists of:\n  (1) the method, e.g., GET.\n  (2) if it is the result of a redirection, a string that indicates so.\n  (3) the URL associated with that request.\n\nTo search for a specific record in the log, use the ‘Search in log’ option from the option menu. The option will be available when you open the menu while the log is opened.\n\nUsing the back button of the device (or an equivalent gesture) will close the log.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title2">2. Usage</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_1">i. Load a URL</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_1">To load a URL, paste it to the URL field and then tap ‘Load’.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_2">ii. Search the web</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_2">To do search, firstly set the search URL in settings and enter the keyword, and then tap ‘Search’.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_3">iii. Search a web page</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_3">To do search in a web page, use the ‘search content’ option from the option menu (only available if any page is loaded).\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_4">iv. View the source code</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_4">To see the source code of a web page, add ‘view-source:’ to the start of the URL that points to it. For example: ‘<code>view-source:https://example.com/index.html</code>’. This usage is supported through the framework.\n\nAlternatively, you can use the ‘view the source code of this page’ option hidden in the menu that is opened by tapping the three-dot icon and then tapping ‘more’.\n\nTo search in the source code, you may use the ‘search content’ option as if it were a normal web page.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_5">v. Console and REPL</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_5">To use the console and REPL features, input some code (should normally be JS code) into the URL field and use the ‘Run’ button (enabled in settings) to execute it. The execution of such code, even in the console mode, is never handled by this app, but by the framework or system. This app only implemented the logic to display the log messages.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_6">vi. Logging</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_6">The ‘foreground logging’ feature gives you some meta-information about the page you are reading. The format of it is the same as that of a log entry. See above for more details.\n</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_7">vii. Using this app as a generalized intent sender or activity launcher</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_7">By using some code that looks like ‘<b><code>location.href=\"intent:#Intent;...;end\"</code></b>’, you can utilize this app as a generalized intent sender and activity launcher (by specifying ‘action’, ‘component’, etc. in the form of text), with the restriction that, the intent can only be sent to an app other than this application. For security concerns, this app will refuse to send such an intent if it detects its own package name in the URI or intent, in which case it can show an error message and might not log.\n\nIntent scheme URIs are half-supported by this app. That is to say, they will usually be processed correctly, but this app usually doesn\'t check if a URI is an ‘<b><code>intent:</code></b>’ URI, except when trying to protect itself from intent-based attacks. (See https://www.mbsd.jp/Whitepaper/IntentScheme. for information about this issue.)\n\nInstead, `<b><code>intent:</code></b>` URIs will be treated as if they were URIs of unrecognized schemes (such as ‘<b><code>abc://</code></b>’), for any of which this app will ask the user whether to launch an intent, except in the specific situations mentioned above.</string>
    <string name="settings_activity_label">Settings</string>
    <string name="doc_activity_label">Documentation</string>
    <string name="certificate">Certificate</string>
    <string name="cert_part1">"Version: %1$d\n\nSerial number: %2$s\n\nSignature algorithm: %3$s\n\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_part2">"Issuer: %1$s\n\nValidity:\n    Not before: %2$s\n    Not after: %3$s\n\nSubject: %4$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_part3">"\nPublic key of the subject:\n    Algorithm: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameters_s">"    Parameters: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameters_lf">"    Parameters:\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_a_s">"        a: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_b_s">"        b: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_g_s">"        g: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_h_d">"        h: %1$d\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_m_d">"        m: %1$d\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_n_s">"        n: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_p_s">"        p: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_q_s">"        q: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_parameter_point_g">"        G:\n            x: %1$s\n            y: %2$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_point_w">"    W:\n        x: %1$s\n        y: %2$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_value_u_s">"    u: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_value_y_s">"    y: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_x_is_odd">"    x is odd: %1$s\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_modulus_exponent">"    Modulus: %1$s\n    Exponent: %2$d\n"</string>
    <string name="cert_final_part">"\nSignature algorithm: %1$s\n\nSignature: %2$s\n"</string>
    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="theme_default">Default (System default or Dark)</string>
    <string name="theme_dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="theme_light">Light</string>
</resources>
